Sir!
Oh, pardon me, coming through.
We should expect this sort of thing by now.
He's likely just sightseeing again.
Be that as it may,
don't you think he should show a bit more respect for his position?
We can't have him wondering about whenever he sees fit.
Admiral Aokiji is one of Navy Headquarters' ultimate powerhouses, after all.
Can't say I'm surprised to see a bounty on this kid's head.
His whole family's full of troublemakers.
Proud man, Silver Fox Foxy!
Hey, Captain! Stop fooling around and lend me a hand for a sec!
Whoa! Now that's what I call a tidal wave!
Ooh, scary!
Looks like he's having fun.
Tell me about it.
I bet he'll be laughing even if the ship gets capsized.
Forget that. We need to worry about the mast snapping before anything else.
It can really break? Then what's gonna happen to us?
Don't get so worked up.
Even if the mast does end up breaking,
that doesn't mean the ship will sink.
And we've got a navigator, don't we?
She's smart and cute enough to get us out of any store.
We need to worry about the mast snapping before anything else.
It can really break? Then what's gonna happen to us?
Don't get so worked up!
Even if the mast does end up breaking,
that still doesn't mean the ship will sink!
Huh?
Hey! How's it going? Long time no see!
Oh, wow! Look, it's Straw Hat!
Hey! Hey!
I won't stand for a straw hat!
Don't even look at us!
We haven't sucked in so low that we'd beg for help
from one of our sworn enemies!
Hey!
Okay, see ya!
Wait! But if you want to help us,
we're okay with that, you know!
Hey, boss.
Behind you.
Nothing to be afraid of!
Slow, slow beam!
Beam!
We're going down!
Oh, that wave looks pretty bad!
A tiny boat like that won't stand a chance in this weather!
Hold on, I got it!
Huh?
Here!
Grab this!
Oh, I meant grab the rope, not my arm, you dummy!
No way!
It's not the...
Yeah, my ass!
No way!
Whoa!
You...
Well, this is all that's left of me.
My crew is gone, the sexy fox is gone,
and now I don't even have a ship to sail with.
This is the end of the sail for Fox.
I might as well face the music.
I'm a fool.
It would have been better for everyone
if I just let myself sink to the bottom of the ocean.
Mars, no.
So you think he's faking it, or what?
In my expert opinion, I'd say yes.
Make pity on me!
At this point, I have nowhere to go
and no one else to turn to.
Let me stay on your ship, I'm begging you!
Sure, why not?
You don't have your own, and you gotta go somewhere.
Here, have a little soup.
We wouldn't want you catching a cold.
Wow, that looks great!
I think I'll share some with Choppy.
Hey, Sanji, me too!
This is all I have left.
I'll cook you some more tomorrow.
Something wrong?
You can help yourself.
What are you trying to pour?
It's not really soup if there's nothing in it!
How about I put you in the soup?
Would you like that?
Huh?
You ain't great!
Foxy, apologize before he murders you!
Quick!
What?
Oh my gosh, look at all this stuff!
They've got gold and jewels and everything!
Why didn't anybody tell me the straw hats were so rich?
Oh, shoot, the soup's getting cold!
Choppy, where are you?
Choppy!
Louie, guess it was just a candle holder.
Where's boss?
How's that, Choppy?
They don't honestly expect me to fish, do they?
That's not how you treat a guest.
Besides, if I want something to eat, I can just grab one of these oranges!
Should have figured.
It can't be.
Boss, I see the sexy Foxy!
You what?
Ahoy!
Does that mean you're getting off our ship?
Did someone say they're leaving?
Over here!
Sodium.
Hydrogen phosphate.
She's still looking for me?
No, they all went back to their old ship.
Ah.
You guys, even after we were separated, you still couldn't forget about your old boss.
Oh, I see, I see.
Well, you can all come back to the Foxy Pirates now, so there's no need to cry.
Come on, it's okay.
Now that everyone's together again, it'll be just like old times.
I hate to break it to you, Foxy, but I'm afraid that's not possible.
Says who?
Don't make me throw you off my ship!
Your ship?
This ship belongs to the Fang Frog Pirates now.
In other words, these men are my underlings, not yours.
Huh?
Fang Frog?
Who are they?
Oh, they're those pirates we ran into who lost half of their crew to Foxy in a Davey Bat fight.
But this time, Foxy's the one who lost all his stuff to them.
Wow, that must suck for Splithead.
That's what he gets for winning all of his crew members for some stupid game.
I'll pass on the deal for farewell, thank you.
Come on, let's go.
We're done here.
Not so fast.
We still have some business to settle.
You see, some of these new recruits of mine are still a bit too attached to their former boss.
That is to say, I can't get them to take off those ridiculous-looking masks.
And frankly, it's turning into quite an eyesore.
The captain has to earn the respect of his crew, you know.
It doesn't come free.
Whoa.
Is it just me or is Foxy kind of cool all of a sudden?
He's okay for a Splithead.
Respect, you say?
Well, in the world of pirates, the weak do tend to flock to the strong, don't they?
In that case, if I want them to come to their senses,
all I have to do is defeat their old boss in a fight.
I challenge you, Silver Fox Foxy.
You want to fight me again, do you?
I'll beat you as many times as it takes.
Uh-oh, he's gonna accept.
Hey, come over here and check this out, quick.
Splithead's on fire over there.
He's on fire?
That sounds dangerous.
I'm not sure.
Have a little more faith in your captain, Porcha.
You should be happy.
We'll have our old ship and our old crew back in no time.
Now, why don't we make it official?
As captain of the Foxy Pirates,
I challenge you Fang Frogs to a diving back fight.
Watch and learn.
I'll show you what a real captain is made of.
You wanted to prove you were stronger than me?
Then why don't we start this game off with a little duel?
Strictly between us captains, of course.
I trust you have no objection to that.
He's pretty confident, isn't he?
With his powers, I would be too.
So you think he's gonna use them?
Well, yeah.
What else would he do?
Here I come.
Slow, slow beam!
Now's your chance, men.
Take him out!
You're not much of a threat
once that annoying little beam of yours is taken care of.
Not so funny when it happens to you, Hite!
Hold on, boss!
What do you think you're doing?
Hold it right there.
Drop your weapon.
Wow, pretty pathetic, huh?
Only a fool would stay loyal to a captain like him.
What's wrong with you?
This was supposed to be a duel between captains,
you big cheater.
You don't know anything, kid.
It's true that Foxy challenged me to a duel,
but I never said I accepted.
The jerk's asking for it.
Calm down, Luffy.
It's up to Foxy to win this fight on his own.
Butting in won't do anyone any good.
This horseman is right.
Just sit back and watch, Straw Hat.
Yeah?
I'll put my pride on the line
and show you what the Silver Fox can really do.
Wow, check out that thing up there!
Hey, the Fox guy's gone.
Did anyone see where he went?
He went that way.
Trust me, I would never ever lie.
Great, thanks.
You think we'd fall for that?
I wonder if they're having a party or something without me.
Maybe I should go up there and check it out.
Oh?
I thought you wanted to stay and play games with me.
But if you'd rather have that girl chase you around,
that's fine too.
Oh!
Kay, it's your turn, Robin.
There you go!
One roasted fox coming up!
No!
Stop right there!
I'll teach you who's the captain around here if it kills you!
Hey, I thought you were only supposed to use weapons on your enemies.
It doesn't make much sense to turn them on your men, if you ask me.
Oh?
If you think you can rule with violence and fear alone,
then you're nothing but a bully bossing around a bunch of thugs.
It takes a hell of a lot more than that to be the captain of a ship.
You're better off just giving up now.
Give up on my ship and crew, too.
It pulls you around, even though it certainly attacks you.
Because as long as I'm here, I'll fight for them, with all the power I've got!
Grr...
Shut your-
AHHHHH!
BOOSTO!
Hey! Split Head! Hang in there, it's not over yet!
Come on...
Oh... It's you, Straw Head.
I guess that was pretty pathetic, wasn't it?
But say, would you do me a favor? Just this once.
Here.
I want you to have this.
That match of ours, even if I lost.
It was the best time of my life.
No, it can't be.
Give everything to me.
I'm gonna get your groove back, Foxman.
I'm your opponent now!
But I warn you, faint frog pirates!
This Afro don't take prisoners!
So funky!
Now hold on a second, this has nothing to do with you!
It does now!
Well, that's too bad, because I don't want to fight a guy with a 100 million barry bounty on his head.
I got too much to lose and nothing to gain!
How stupid can you be?
If you win, that bounty will be yours!
And that's in addition to the 60 million barry you'll get for his swordsman!
Now let me share a secret with you!
I've been on Strawhead's ship, and he's got a whole mountain of gold tucked away in there!
Needless to say, I'm sure that's worth quite a bit!
You're pirates, aren't you? Then grab that booty!
That's what we get for letting them stay on our ship!
Why is he bragging? It's not his treasure.
I'd better check later to make sure nothing is missing.
Did he say mountain of gold?
He sure did!
Repair the cannon, men! We're taking out Strawhead!
Yeah!
Fire!
That looks like fun!
Yeah!
Go on, I know you want to-
What was that?
Hand over the gold knife!
Looks like we'll have to take out the whole crew, huh? What a pain.
Ha! You think you could beat all 500 of us? Get him, men!
What? We can't hear you!
Hey!
Well, that's too bad. I guess it's just you and me, huh?
Check out that thing up there!
Huh?
Hey! You tricked me!
Fah!
Fah! Fah! Fah! Fah!
Salfang Frog! How do you like that Afro soul?!
Is it too wild? You can't handle it?!
How does it feel to go head to head with the only pirate in the world strong enough to defeat me?!
Fah! Fah! Fah! Fah! Fah!
Ha! Ha!
Go easy on these losers. We don't want to kill them.
Not everyone has superhuman strength, you know.
Ha!
Sword... catch!
Catch.
There better be a damn good explanation for this.
You can't play innocent with me. I saw you push Nami down.
Yeah, cause she would've gotten a spear to the face if I hadn't.
And what if she'd hurt her beautiful face when she fell?
Don't you know how to treat a lady? You gotta be more gentle.
Sword. Catch.
So are you gonna let me beat this guy up or not?
No way! Put him down and go apologize to Nami!
If you want to fight that bad, I'll give you one!
Out of the way!
Look, human fireworks.
They must really be going at it.
Oh, my ulcerative colitis!
Hey, you're not dying, are you?
Ah!
Sorry, youngster, but with age comes wisdom.
Oh, that's no good. Don't worry, I'm a doctor. Let me take a look.
I hate doctors!
Hm, that was just my ketchup star.
Oh, my back! My back!
Come on, was it that back?
Ah!
That was splendid, Straw Hat!
Splendid straw hat is simply marvelous. I have to admit the couldn't have done it better myself
What can I say? I owe it all to your passion brother
There's just one more thing. I want to tell you
No worries you and I are friends you don't have to thank me
You should have learned your lesson by now straw hat everyone knows the silver fox never forgets a grudge
And he always gets what he wants
Your fate was sealed the moment you set foot on a ship. Did you think I would take that humiliating defeat sitting down?
No, not even a rematch would satisfy me a hundred and sixty million Barry and a nice pile of gold might help though
You it is
This time I'll sell things once and for all and you'll have no choice but to admit that the foxy pirates are the strongest in the world
Virtue World
That's it!
One Piece, the guy who's the closest to Invincible and the most dangerous man!
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!